(Raj:)On the off chance that Bernadette
doesn't call back and apologize,
(Raj:)how do you feel about Mexican food
for dinner tonight?
(Howard:)I don't know.
Sounds kind of heavy.
(Raj:)That's 'cause you always fill up
on chips.
(Amy:)And this is Dr. Gunderson
from Stockholm.
(Sheldon:)Ah, Sweden.
(Sheldon:)Home of my favourite Muppet
and second favourite meatball.
(Sheldon:)Okay, the Nordic reputation
for lack of humor is well-founded.
(Sheldon:)Boy, is his name Gunderson
or No-Funderson?
(Amy:)Where are we going with this,
Dr. Cooper?
(Sheldon:)Please, I'm your boyfriend.
You call me Sheldon.
(Penny:)That's right,
I am in a boy-girl relationship
(Sheldon:)with this cute little lump of wool.
(Penny:)-Sheldon...
-it's a physical relationship, too.
(Sheldon:)Hand-holding, hugging...
even on hot days.
Ow!
Okay, here's a new ons.
(Sheldon:)Apparently now we kick each other
in the shin under the table.
(Sheldon:)How do you like it
when I do it to you?